 export const Questions=[
    {
        prompt:"Who is the primeMinsiter of India?",
        OptionA:"Narendra Modi",
        OptionB:"lalau Yadav",
        OptionC:"Arvind Kejriwal",
        OptionD:"Pappu Bhai",
        Answer:"OptionA"

    },
    {
        prompt:"Which is the programming language?",
        OptionA:"Hindi",
        OptionB:"French",
        OptionC:"Javascript",
        OptionD:"Titanic",
        Answer:"OptionC"
        
    },
    {
        
        prompt:"What is the range of values that can be stored by int datatype in C?",
        OptionA:"2^31",
        OptionB:"454664654",
        OptionC:"8445645",
        OptionD:"7845515100",
        Answer:"OptionA"

    },
    {
        prompt:"Who is the father of C language?", 
        OptionA: "Steve Jobs",
        OptionB: "James Gosling",
        OptionC: "Dennis Ritchie",
        OptionD: "Rasmus Lerdor",
        Answer:"OptionC"
,
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
        OptionA: "int number",
        OptionB: "float rate",
        OptionC: "int variable_count",
        OptionD: "int $main",
        Answer:"OptionD"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which is valid C expression?",
        OptionA: "int my_num=100000",
        OptionB: "int_my_num=100000",
        OptionC: "int my num=1000",
        OptionD: "int $my_num=10000",
        Answer:"OptionA"
    },
    {
        prompt:"What is JavaScript?",
        OptionA:"JavaScript is a scripting language",
        OptionB:"JavaScript is an assembly language",
        OptionC:"JavaScript is a compiled language",
        OptionD:"None of the mentioned",
        Answer:"OptionA"
    },
    {
        prompt:"which statement defines closures in JavaScript,which?",
        OptionA:" enclosed with references to its inner function scope",
        OptionB:" enclosed with references to its lexical environment",
        OptionC:" enclosed with the object to its inner function scope",
        OptionD:"None of the mentioned",
        Answer:"OptionB"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Where is Client-side JavaScript code is embedded within HTML documents?",
        OptionA:"A URL uses the special javascript : code",
        OptionB:"A URL uses the special javascript : protocol",
        OptionC:"A URL uses the special javascript : encoding",
        OptionD:"A URL uses the special javascript : stack",
        Answer:"OptionB"
         
    },
    {
        prompt:"what happens when a JavaScript program is developed on a Unix Machine?",
        OptionA:"work perfectly on a Windows Machine",
        OptionB:"displayed as JavaScript text on the browser",
        OptionC:"throw errors and exceptions",
        OptionD:"restricted to a Unix Machine only",
        Answer:"OptionA"
    }

]